export default [
    {
        id:"questions_1",
        question: "What is the payment model for your services?",
        answer: "Our payment structure depends on the project. We'll share a detailed quote before we start. Typically, we use a payment plan based on project milestones, which includes: An initial payment (50%) for project setup. A second payment (25%) upon reaching a project milestone (around 75% completion). The final payment (25%) before project delivery. We can also follow a payment model based on the hours worked. We'll discuss and decide on the best approach based on your project and needs."
    },
    {   
        id:"questions_2",
        question: "How do I keep track of the project's progress?",
        answer: "We use reliable project management tools such as JIRA to monitor our projects. We keep track of hours worked and project progress. Additionally, you'll receive weekly progress updates from us via email."
    },
    {   
        id:"questions_3",
        question: "Do you provide UI / UX design services?",
        answer: "We encourage clients to provide their own design, as design preferences are highly subjective and may involve multiple revisions to meet your vision. However, if required, we can connect you with a third-party designer for direct design collaboration."
    },
    {   
        id:"questions_4",
        question: "Do you have an enterprise plan?",
        answer: "While we typically work with small businesses, please feel free to get in touch with your specific needs. We're open to discussing your unique needs. However, please be aware that we don't offer credit facilities."
    },
    {   
        id:"questions_5",
        question: "Do I own the code written for my project?",
        answer: "It varies based on the project. For websites without third-party services, we'll provide access to the Github repository, allowing you to own and access the code. However, for more complex projects involving databases, servers, and tasks like web scraping, we retain ownership of the code but will provide you with access to the relevant data."
    },
    {   
        id:"questions_6",
        question: "Who pays for costs such as like cloud services, domain name, etc.?",
        answer: "It is your choice. You can manage your cloud and pay for it, or we can help deploy to your cloud. We recommend AWS for deployment. Similarly, you can buy domain names directly or let us guide you through the process."
    },
    {   
        id:"questions_7",
        question: "Do you charge for meetings?",
        answer: "Before starting a project, we offer 2 hours of free meeting time (phone calls, zoom meetings, google meet, etc.) to understand your requirements and provide a quote. Once the project begins, we provide 4 hours of free monthly meeting time to our clients. Beyond that, meetings are charged at a fixed rate per hour."
    },
    {   
        id:"questions_8",
        question: "Do you provide product management services?",
        answer: "Yes, absolutely. Our team comprises seasoned product managers with over a decade of experience. We offer solution and product management services, although these are typically considered more premium. We often suggest our clients come up with the solution, and we handle the technical implementation."
    },
    {   
        id:"questions_9",
        question: "Who assumes legal liability in case my project violates a law?",
        answer: "Before commencing any project, we require a contract where you assume legal responsibilities and indemnify us for any losses or issues arising from the project. Our commitment to transparency and legal clarity is aimed at safeguarding the interests of both our clients and our team. If you have any questions or require further details regarding this contractual obligation, we are here to assist you."
    },
    {   
        id:"questions_10",
        question: "What other industries have you worked in?",
        answer: "We've proudly served diverse clients in various industries for 10+ years, including Oil & Gas, Publishing Houses, FinTech, Architectural & Interior Design, Logistics, etc."
    },
]